[crickets chirping]
[clatter]
[gentle music]
It looks like a painting.
It doesn't even seem real.
[footsteps approaching]
GIRL: Masie!
[suspenseful music]
Maisie!
[metallic rattle]
[music continues]
Cricket!
[breathing heavily]
Where's dad?
[suspenseful music]
Don't look at it.
Is he gone?
He probably just
ran into town.
I'm hungry.
OK.
Is that a new story?
I'm working.
What's it about?
It's about a fire that
jumps out of a barrel
and chases two sisters.
I'm pretty sure
they're going to die.
Cricket, we
haven't prayed yet.
You pray for an hour.
Lord, I thank you
for this breakfast.
And I thank you for
my sister, who I love.
Lord, I pray for our brother.
Help him to not get lost
out there in the desert.
I pray that dad can get
home before his biscuits get
too cold.
And Lord, please keep
the flies from biting
Darlene too much this summer.
[distant bird squawking]
CRICKET: Maisie!
Maisie!
[birds chirping]
Cricket, you
got to hold still.
Maisie.
Uh-huh?
You look like mom.
[CRICKETS CHIPRING, BIRDS
CHIRPING]
You're not supposed
to go in there.
Dad left it open.
Come on.
[wooden creaking]
What is this place?
It's our sugarhouse.
You don't remember?
We used to come here all
the time during winter
and make syrup.
Why don't we do it anymore?
[melancholy music]
'Cause mom died.
[car approaching]
[ominous music]
[engine whirring]
[car door opens, closes]
Hi there.
Are you Maisie Sire?
Yes, sir.
Is your dad Gage Sire?
Is he in trouble?
No, he's not in trouble.
I just-- I just
need to talk to him.
Is that your sister there?
Yes, sir, that's Cricket.
OFFICER: Who, uh-- who takes
care of you in Cricket?
My dad.
And if for some reason,
he wouldn't come home?
The reason I ask, because
of your age, you two
would have to go
into foster care.
Would they split us up?
I'm not sure what
their policy is.
Cricket's adopted.
Does that matter?
I don't know how they handle
that type of situation either.
Would you possibly
have any other family
that you could live with or
that could look after you two?
We have a brother, Finn.
He could look after us.
OK, I'm familiar with Finn.
Um, I'll stop back by in a
couple of days and touch base
again.
Maybe your dad will be back, OK?
[car door opens, closes]
[engine starts, car revs]
[insects chirping]
[phone chimes]
[phone clicks]
[coyotes howling]
[howls]
[howling continues]
[clatter]
[fridge door closes]
[leaves rustling]
Cricket!
[gentle music]
[thunder cracks, rumbles]
Cricket, there's a storm coming.
We need to get in, hon!
Don't make me come down there!
Cricket!
[thunder rumbles]
[rain pouring]
I love you to the moon.
I love you to
the grocery store.
That's better than last night.
Love you to the toilet.
[chuckles]
Goodnight.
MAISIE: Do you
remember when mom would
stay up with us during storms?
I do.
I remember like
it was yesterday.
[thunder cracks, rumbles]
Cricket, can I stay in
here with you tonight?
[gentle music]
[flies buzzing]
Did you know that cows cry?
It says that when a calf is
taken away from its mother,
the cow will grieve For?
Weeks.
She will have a mournful,
high-pitched cry
and even have tears in her eyes.
Isn't that the saddest
thing you've ever heard?
[car approaching]
[suspenseful music]
Dad?
Hey, girlie, where's it at?
What are you doing?
Got nothing to do with you.
Best go and get Gage, come
out and open up this hood.
He ain't here, is he?
Reckon you wish he was.
Got your stuffed
lamb running loose.
Cricket get inside!
[breathing heavily]
Go on, handle your business.
We'll just take what we want.
Don't rush me, Floyd.
You think I can't smell it.
[metallic bang]
Come on, go.
[breathing heavily]
Closet, go.
CRICKET: What's happening?
I can't see.
QUAID: No, I will find it.
I'm going to find him.
CRICKET: Are you going
to call the police?
[muffled conversation]
Maisie, I'm scared.
Can you come sit with me?
[rattling]
QUAID: Over there.
I don't care where they are.
[tense music]
Did you call?
They'll take you away from me.
[muffled conversation continues]
Dear God, please
make them go away.
Make them go away.
[car doors close]
[engine starts]
[vehicle receding]
Are they gone?
I think so.
What if they come back?
Who are you calling?
Finn.
[gentle music]
[animals chirping]
[bird squawking]
[phone chimes]
[gentle music]
CRICKET: Maisie!
Maisie!
[chatter, laughter]
I want macaroni.
In a minute.
[tv noise]
Ow.
MAN (ON TV): Hey, get back here.
Don't worry, ma'am,
I'm a professional.
Ow.
Oh, sorry.
[chatter]
What are you doing?
Playing hopscotch.
That's not how you play.
You're weird.
[whistle blows]
[melancholy music]
Cricket!
Do you need a tow?
Maisie.
[thud]
[cricket screams]
Cricket!
FINN: I got to see that.
Oh, yeah, it's just so much.
I can't even tell you
how much I've learned.
Hey, Maisie Mae.
You want to hug a ghost?
You about made
my heart jump out.
You know that, right?
What do you want with a heart?
Mm.
I'm glad you're home.
Oh, well, we'll
see about that.
I've got a truckload
of dead bodies.
You want to see?
Wow.
Where did you get all this?
Oh, that first
house off the highway.
Seriously, Finn?
They shouldn't
have left it outside.
Where are we going to put that?
Crawling on the house.
Nice.
Oh, wait.
I need a picture.
Hang on.
[exhales deeply]
[blows raspberries]
[mimics choking]
CRICKET: Take it already.
Finn, look normal.
This is normal.
Come on!
OK, got it.
[cricket chirping, dog barking]
How about that?
You can't jump three
in a row like that.
That's not in the rules.
Yes, I can.
No, you can't.
- Yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
Yes, I can.
Says who?
Says the cow.
Oh.
[giggles]
I don't mind
sleeping on the couch.
It's OK.
I put some more
hangers in the closet,
and I just cleared
out the top drawer.
Oh, and look at this.
Mr. Gill.
[chuckles] I found him
in the attic for you.
I wanted you to feel at home.
[pensive music]
Did you hear from Dad?
FINN: Just you.
Where do you think he is?
Out looking for something.
Um, Cricket was wanting to
go pick pumpkins tomorrow.
It'd be nice, us doing
family stuff again.
Sure.
Awesome.
OK, well, I'll let you sleep.
Good night, Finn.
Night.
[gentle music]
[insects chirping]
[groans]
[pants]
Hey, Finn, look.
I found mine.
Looks just like you.
Where's yours?
Right there.
[flies buzzing]
MAISIE: You can't pick that one.
FINN: Why not?
Because why would
anyone choose that?
Hey, Cricket, come help
me find Finn a pumpkin.
CRICKET: OK.
[insects chirping]
[gulping]
Hey, are you giving
away my pumpkin seeds?
[drink dribbling]
She just licked
them a little bit.
I know where your heart is.
[chuckles]
Finn, remember, this is my God.
This is my family.
And they are my heart.
[chuckles] Mom
taught you that, right?
She taught you too.
Remember those
rabbits she got for you?
Oh, my gosh, they
were so precious.
They tore holes in
all of the carpets.
That one tore a
hole in the TV cord.
And she made them
the cutest little hats.
She made hats for the rabbits?
More like bonnets, but
they looked so sweet.
[scoffs]
Every time Dad
saw a rabbit, he'd
tell me to go fetch a shovel.
Dad liked my rabbits.
You always think like that.
Like what?
Nothing.
How do you think?
I don't.
I'm just a shovel.
[birdsong]
MAISIE: Finn, look.
It's God's fingers.
Wh-- what are
you talking about?
Don't you see it?
[creaking]
I'm not wearing this again.
Oh, you look adorable.
I've worn this
since I was four.
MAISIE: Well, we can put some
black leggings underneath.
Oh, come on, Cricket.
It's time to get rid
of that old sheepskin.
Finally.
It's time to run
with the wolves.
[imitating wolves howling]
All right, she's ready.
She can't go like that.
CRICKET: Why not?
She's a devil.
That's right.
[snarling]
Hey, come on, Cricket.
Wait.
Can I come?
What are you supposed to be?
A veterinarian.
[sighs] I-- I don't think so.
You could stay here
and pass out candy.
We don't have candy,
because nobody ever comes.
[dog barking]
[spooky music]
[growling]
[screams]
[chuckles]
Hey, how about this one?
The lights are off.
So?
If the lights are off,
you're not supposed to knock.
It's the rules.
Halloween's got no rules.
[sighs]
Here.
[knocking on door]
Trick or treat?
I don't have
nothing to give you.
Can't you see?
The light's not on.
You're gonna send my little
sister home without a treat?
I told you I
don't have nothing.
I said, "trick or treat?"
What about that did
you not understand?
I don't have nothing.
I know.
But it's Halloween,
so I got no choice.
See, I might just put
a mouse in your mailbox
or maybe throw a rock
through a window.
Maybe I'll set your car on fire.
Yeah, that's the thing.
You never know.
I've got some butter
cookies in the cabinet.
Now we're talking.
Works every time.
[pensive music]
[flames crackling]
[car engine humming]
[grim music]
[clacking]
[sighs]
CRICKET: I'm not touching that.
MAISIE: Well, my hand
won't fit in the drain.
Yuck.
[water sloshing]
Can you feel it?
I can't find it.
I'm stuck!
[screams]
Finn!
I'm stuck!
[bird cawing]
Cricket, time for breakfast.
Finn.
[pensive music]
Check it out.
Dad's old jacket.
There's probably
spiders in it.
This is tough.
Finn, are you leaving?
Yeah.
Why?
You've got things handled.
No, I really don't.
Dad will be back.
But we need you here.
Well, I need to
be somewhere else.
[swing squeaking]
Maisie.
Mhm.
[car engine humming]
[ominous music]
Go get Finn.
Finn, they're here!
Who's here?
Them.
[car engine stops]
Hey there, chipmunk.
You look like you
done seen the devil.
MAISIE: Finn!
Gage?
Maisie, get inside
Well, you ain't Gage.
You Schmitz?
You need to go.
[thumps on door]
You hear that, Floyd?
Schmitz says we need to get.
I have a feeling
like Floyd needs
to stick around a little bit.
We came here for
a package, wrapped
up kind of like a sausage.
Gage was the last
one who has seen it.
Well, he's gone.
QUAID: So maybe you
know something about it.
What you hiding there, hoss?
[cackles] Big man.
Finn, get inside.
There's nothing here for you.
Where's my package?
Ask Schmitz.
Watch yourself, darling.
He's got the smell of it on him.
[car doors slamming]
[car engine starts]
All right.
[solemn music]
It's so quiet.
Mom always said to
listen to the birds,
because God takes care of them,
and he'll take care of you too.
But I can't hear a thing.
[food package rumpling]
Cricket, seriously, use a bowl.
Finn says I don't need a bowl.
It's all going in my mouth.
What happened to your hair?
I'm going natural.
Did Finn teach you that too?
[munching]
[groans] I don't
want the light.
Finn, did you see this?
I'm sleeping.
Well, it says that we
owe tax on the house.
I thought we only
paid tax at the store.
Finn, can you please help?
I don't know what to do.
[finn groans]
[car engine humming]
[chatter]
Ow.
[school bell ringing]
Maisie, come on in.
So senior year, very exciting.
Yes, ma'am.
Are you looking forward
to your senior trip?
Lake of the Ozarks
should be a blast.
Please have a seat.
So we're here to
talk about college.
Yes, ma'am.
I brought my application.
Oh, you wanna
be a veterinarian.
You must be an animal lover.
Oh, my gosh, yes, even
before I could walk.
TEACHER: Is that so?
My mom always said
I was half rabbit.
[chuckles] Oh,
that's adorable.
Maisie, you know, it's not
easy to get into vet school.
I know my grades aren't
the best right now.
It's expensive too.
Do your parents
have a college fund?
Maisie, can I be
straight with you?
If you wanna go to
college, you need
to get a scholarship,
which means
you need to get your grades up.
OK.
It means more
time on homework.
It means after-school tutoring.
And you need to find
ways to stand out.
Maybe you could volunteer at
an animal shelter on weekends.
I don't have a
lot of free time.
Maisie, this is
your dream, right?
Yes, ma'am.
TEACHER: What are you
willing to sacrifice for it?
[chair scraping]
[hinges squealing]
Cricket, let me
help you with that.
[bell tolls]
[dog barking]
[metal clanking]
[clacking]
Coob?
Finn Saier.
[groans] Oh, my God.
[chuckles] I thought
you were your dad.
[chuckles] I heard you
run off with the circus.
[chuckles] Uh, who said that?
I did, to a lot of people.
[both laugh]
Hey, there's been
worse said about me.
Someone said you skipped
town with your old man.
What else have you heard?
All I know is.
I can't get any
ice in this town.
[grim music]
Is that right?
Yeah.
I might help with that.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[whoosh]
[car engine humming]
[coins rattling]
Sorry.
We're not open.
Can I get a job?
Why aren't you in school?
Because I'm done with it.
[car engine humming]
[christmas carol]
[door opens, closes]
Hey.
You put up the tree without me.
I told him to wait.
What happened to my ornament?
CRICKET: Finn dropped it.
How about this?
I'll break one of mine,
and we'll be even, OK?
[ornament cracks]
I made that!
[laughs]
I'll just break two
of mine then, OK?
No, just stop
breaking everything!
[door slams]
We should have
waited for Maisie.
[insects chirping]
[car engine starts]
[vehicle leaving]
[sighs]
Aren't you gonna pray?
God, I thank
you for Christmas.
I thank you for this food,
and I thank you for cricket.
And, God, I pray for Finn, even
though I don't feel like it.
Amen.
[wind howling]
[clatter]
Cricket, can you do
that outside, please?
It's cold.
[grim music]
Cricket.
Cricket?
[gasps]
Where's my jumprope?
It's in your hand.
Here.
See?
Where's my jumprope?
[car engine humming]
Did I amaze you, Mai?
Merry Christmas.
We already had Christmas.
It's over now.
But I got you a present.
Did you steal him
from the Nativity?
Yeah, I did.
It isn't funny, Finn.
Cricket and I, we
opened presents,
and we built a snowman.
You missed it all.
Come on.
I got him for you.
You should have
got him for yourself.
[somber music]
[door slams]
[sighs]
[chatter]
[bell rings]
All right, class,
let's get ready to go.
GIRL: Bye, Ms. Patty.
Bye.
Cricket.
Cricket?
[phone vibrating, ringing]
Maisie, no phones, please.
Sorry.
NURSE (ON PHONE): Yes, this
message is for Maisie Saier.
I'm the nurse at
Eagle Elementary,
and your sister, Cricket,
um, she just had a seizure.
We've been trying to
reach your father, Gage,
but he won't respond.
Could you please
come right away?
I can tell you more
when you arrive.
All right, thank you.
Bye.
Hey, what did I
say about phones?
[sighs] It's my sister.
I need to get her.
After the shift.
Come on.
[keypad tone]
[sniffling]
[line ringing]
Come on, Finn.
[machines whirring]
[beeping]
[shouts]
[cackling]
[phone ringing, vibrating]
What are you now up to?
Uh, it's cold.
It is cold as a walrus's butt.
That's what I know.
[chuckles]
I think a walrus's butt
would get pretty toasted.
You wanna reach your
hand down there and check?
No.
[phone vibrating]
That your girlfriend calling?
It's nothing.
Oh, come on.
Pick it up, loverboy.
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
I could-- I could step outside.
If the two of you wanna
climb in the back, I can--
[shrieks] who's the baby?
Chill.
It's just a baby Jesus.
That's the story, ain't it?
You don't wanna hear it.
Well, you need to
get it out of here.
What?
I ain't buying no glass
with baby Jesus staring at me.
I ain't lying.
Put something over his eyes!
[sighs]
[phone vibrating]
Hey, loverboy, your
girl is calling again.
[chuckles] Hey, come on.
[door slams]
[line ringing]
Maisie, uh, we've got
tables that need bussing.
Did you hear me?
You're a quitter, aren't you?
You don't know me.
Automatism can happen
during a seizure.
It's when you repeat a motion
without being aware of it.
Have you noticed anything
unusual with Cricket, things
like staring into space
or rapid blinking?
On Christmas, it was,
like, she just froze up.
Maisie, we need to have
Cricket see a neurologist.
They would be able to
diagnose if this is epilepsy.
Is that dangerous?
It's treatable
with medication.
She can still have
a normal life.
But there's risk of
more serious seizures,
and those can be scary.
It's important to keep
Cricket away from stress.
How have things been at home?
[pensive music]
[car engine humming]
Do you remember this?
Maybe.
[yells]
Maisie.
Why did you call?
Because Cricket had a
seizure, and I lost my job.
And I can't go to
college anymore.
None of that matters to you.
[pensive music]
[car engine humming]
Morning, Maisie Mai.
You just woke up?
I thought you ran off.
What?
I just went into town,
paid off that tax bill.
I stopped by the farm
store and got all this.
What is it?
New taps, Mason jars,
everything we need.
I thought we might get
the sugarhouse going.
Are you serious?
I don't joke about syrup.
[intriguing music]
Come on.
[tractor engine sputters]
[cheers]
[simmering]
I've already put Cricket to bed.
Yeah, she was worn out.
So that's the last of it?
Yeah, it's a
pretty good batch.
We could sell a lot
come springtime.
Are you gonna be around?
[sighs]
Being a brother
suits you, Finn.
So why do you wanna leave?
I just need to.
That's not an answer.
Look, I don't know
what to tell you.
Tell me something.
When I'm here,
I turn into him.
Dad?
What's wrong with that?
Don't you see it?
[grim music]
[phone vibrating]
Don't you want a drink?
Look around, Darlene.
[sighs] It's all
so pretty again.
Don't you think?
[ominous music]
Cricket, you have
to take the pill.
I don't want to.
Please.
No.
[toilet flushes]
Did you flush that
pill down the toilet?
Sit down.
These are expensive.
[pills rattling]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Open up.
No.
Please.
MAISIE: You just have to--
CRICKET: No.
MAISIE: Yes, come on.
Cricket, please.
CRICKET: No.
I cannot get her
to take this pill.
Give me that.
If you fetch my hat, I'll
throw this in the trash.
Yes.
Finn, that's her
seizure medicine.
Now, finish that up.
We've got a lot
of stuff to sell.
[intriguing music]
Hey, Cricket.
How are you doing?
Good.
How's it going, Mr. Miller.
Finn, how are you?
Thank you, Mr. Miller.
All right, thank you, kids.
[chatter and laughter]
[grim music]
[knocking on door]
Girl, you act like
you've seen a ghost.
Dad.
Maisie Mai.
I knew you'd come back.
How'd you know that?
Because you're my dad.
[chuckles]
Finn, Cricket,
look who's here.
Kept the place up.
Cricket, you done all grown up.
What are you, a
foot, 2 foot taller?
[chuckles]
Hm.
Didn't expect to find you here.
Why'd you leave?
Always right to the business.
We don't have
to talk about it.
Dad's probably wanting
to get settled in.
Nah, I don't
wanna bother y'all.
I'll just sleep out in the shop.
I need a few things.
All grown up.
Thought you were out west.
Maisie needed me.
Man of the house.
Go ahead, boy.
Ask what you wanna ask.
You should tell all of us.
You think they would
understand, like you and me?
Look, I'm a no-good dog.
Everybody knows that.
[chuckles]
Tell you what, boy, you
keep sleeping in my bed
long enough, who knows
what you'll become?
[water gushing]
All right, let's pray.
Lord, thank you for
this food and thank
you for keeping cricket safe.
I pray you can
always protect her.
And Lord, please,
cheer up Darlene.
She hasn't been doing
too well lately.
And Lord, thank you
for bringing Dad home
so we can all be a family again.
Amen.
Are you sure you don't
need another blanket?
Uh, no, hon, I sleep hot.
Good night, Dad.
Yep.
[pensive music]
[insects chirping]
[laughter]
[chatter]
Did you get your
snapshot taken?
I couldn't get
Cricket to hold still.
Hey, boy, think you could,
uh, give me a ride into town?
No trucks.
You just ain't gonna make it.
Can I get out of this shirt?
A little dirt
never hurt nothing.
Come on.
Let's go.
See you for dinner.
[chatter]
[dogs barking]
GAGE: Hey, boy.
What is this?
Baby Jesus.
[bottles clinking]
You remember this, don't you?
Yeah.
I reckon the whole town does.
What was it?
Little league championship game?
And you released how many
mice onto this field?
80.
80 mice.
Didn't some of them jump
over into that concession
stand over there?
[laughs] Yeah.
They had to rescue one of
them from the cheese sauce.
[both laughing]
You, uh-- you
remember the first
thing that I said to the cops
when I come and pick you up?
[pensive music]
"Where's my little outlaw?"
Little outlaw.
I'll take one of those.
[car engine humming]
[car door opens]
[laughter and chatter]
[knocking]
GAGE: What was that?
[laughter]
I wonder if you have colic.
Has your stomach
been hurting you?
I feel like everything's
coming undone.
Dad and Finn, all they wanna do
is hang out in the sugarhouse.
They hardly have time for us.
[donkey snorts]
But I have you.
I'll always have you.
[footsteps]
GAGE: Girls.
Dad.
Yep.
Darlene hasn't been
feeling too well lately.
She barely drinks her water,
and all she wants to do
is lay in the grass.
Well, she is old.
But I'm worried about her.
Do you think we could have a vet
come out and take a look at her?
There was that one
friend of Mom's.
No, I don't want her out here.
It's hard, isn't it,
watching her suffer?
Tell you what.
I'll have somebody come out.
Thanks, Dad.
You bet.
Did you take
your pill, Cricket?
Mm-hmm.
[door hinges creaking]
[somber music]
Maisie.
[gasps]
You need to get out of
here before Dad comes back.
Do you know about this?
You just need to
leave it lie, OK?
What would happen if
Cricket came in here?
We have to call the police.
You can't call the police.
Why not?
Because he's my dad.
He's my dad too.
What?
[sighs]
He's not your dad.
After me, Mom couldn't
have kids anymore.
She always wanted a girl.
You're not my brother?
I'm sorry.
[insects chirping]
[dog barking]
So where are the girls?
What?
I'll look upstairs.
Are you coming to dinner?
No.
What if I make pie?
Will you please shut the door?
(WHISPERING)
Always take the pie.
[pensive music]
[insects chirping]
Did Mom ever talk
to you about me?
Do you think she loved me
the same way I love you?
[tools clinking]
[chatter]
[car engine starts]
I gotta check on something.
[cricket crying]
Cricket, don't look at it.
Don't look at it.
[car engine humming]
Let's go see Darlene.
Let's get this
thing out of here.
[gentle music]
Darlene.
Darlene!
No, no, no, no, no.
Maisie.
Hold on, Maisie.
Hold on!
No!
[door slams]
Get that out of here!
[car engine starts]
Maisie.
Maisie, It's OK.
Maisie--
Get off of me.
No!
[sobbing]
Maisie.
You killed her!
She-- she was sick.
Ask the vet.
No, you're lying!
She just needed help,
but you killed her!
It was the right thing to do.
Nothing you do is right!
I know what you're
doing in the sugarhouse.
You think you know something.
I think the police
might wanna know.
My own daughter
couldn't turn me in.
What'd you call me?
I see who you are now.
[car engine sputters]
Come on!
Maisie!
I need you to bury
this down at the gully!
What's going on?
Fetch a shovel!
Go!
[water flowing]
That's everything.
Bury it and meet
me at the truck.
Is it the cops?
Just get it done!
[car engine humming]
Let's go.
[solemn music]
[door opens]
[tires screech]
[car engine humming]
You good?
I'm good.
No, are you good?
You never know.
[door hinges squeal]
[cackles] Look at you
back from the grave.
GAGE: I have a lap
or two left in me.
Bet you're gonna need
him in this racket.
Talk to Mosley?
What do you want me to say?
How about don't shoot me?
[cackling]
Schmitz?
Who's Schmitz?
Ah, you're kidding me, right?
GAGE: That's my boy, Finn.
I told you about him.
Well, Schmitz here tried
to pull a gun on me once.
Well, you probably
had it coming.
Maybe I did.
Come on, Quaid.
He's one of us.
You look like a Schmitz to me.
[clacking]
Cricket.
Finn!
It's OK.
Will you just
please make it stop.
Please, make it stop.
[somber music]
[footsteps]
You know who you're
asking about that?
Hey, boy.
Floyd and I are gonna go
take care of something.
Why don't you hang out here
with old Quaid for a bit?
Dad.
I don't trust this guy.
You shouldn't.
I'm gonna sit over there, and
I'm gonna stare at that wall
until my dad comes back.
[solemn music]
I love you to the moon.
I love you to the stars.
Hey, Schmitz.
Want to kill some time?
I want none of that.
I hear different.
In fact, I hear you
may be slinging.
See?
Yeah, you better
be careful, son.
That's the old man's work.
Unless you want a piece of it.
Come on, boy, look here.
[sniffs] So much more
where that came from.
We're gonna ring that
bell, you and me.
What are you talking about?
You don't know?
Daddy's done, son.
This is our time.
I don't want nothing
to do with you.
You just might.
Pretty little girls back home--
I'm just saying.
Gonna need taken care of.
How about I take care of you?
[cackles] Whoa, boy,
you got some hate on you.
All right, I'll run with it.
Hey, what do you
mean, my dad's done?
Figure it out, kid.
I know how to get to him.
I know how to get to all y'all.
[grim music]
Hey!
[gun cocks]
[scoffs]
Gage, in here.
What'd I tell you?
Took him long enough.
You got it.
My boy got it.
QUAID: The little girl back
home is more intimidating.
But you were happy
about tonight, didn't you?
Put that thing down, man.
It's not even loaded.
[chatter]
What is this?
It's your baptism.
Into what?
Into all this.
Don't you see it?
Come down to it, you would
have stopped him, wouldn't you?
I wasn't thinking.
That's right.
Knew what your blood told you.
There was a time when you
belonged to your mother,
same as me.
And when she died, you and
I, we took on this new blood.
Don't you understand?
This here, this is what we are.
You are my son.
[bottles clink]
[chatter]
[insects chirping]
Dear God, thank
you for this food.
I pray Darlene gets lots
to eat in heaven right now.
And God, thank
you for my sister,
Maisie, who loves me and
takes good care of me.
And God, please bring Finn home.
Amen.
[door hinges squeal]
[solemn music]
[sighs]
What did I do wrong?
Why can't I hear you?
[birdsong]
[phone vibrating, ringing]
Finn.
Maisie, the birds--
they're everywhere.
I hear them too.
Where are you?
The masonry.
I can't get away.
MAISIE (ON PHONE): I'll come.
Maisie, don't come.
It's not safe.
Finn, I'm bringing you home.
[birdsong]
Finn, why'd you run off?
I just had to get out.
Well, we have to go.
Son.
Finn.
Finn, come with me now.
It's no place for you, Maisie.
It's no place for him either.
Hold on.
Stop!
Please!
[pensive music]
Sorry.
Could have done better.
[distant siren wails]
Dad, I left the drugs in
the truck and the gun too.
Well, good thinking.
You were just doing what
your blood told you.
I'll take care of it.
Dad!
Yep.
Let's get you home.
[intriguing music]
[insects chirping]
[laughter and chatter]
Hey, look what I got.
[theme music]